{
    "subject": "resource/Manhattan_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Woody_Allen",
    "human_readable": "Woody Allen stars in the film Manhattan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9400073885917664,
            "question": "In which film did Woody Allen star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.938310980796814,
            "question": "Name a film starring Woody Allen."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.879662275314331,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that Woody Allen starred in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7891054749488831,
            "question": "Who starred in the film Manhattan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7637680172920227,
            "question": "Is Woody Allen known for acting in films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7094298601150513,
            "question": "What movie features Woody Allen as a lead actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6162416338920593,
            "question": "Are there any famous films directed by Woody Allen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3138551115989685,
            "question": "Where was the film Manhattan probably set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2170737385749817,
            "question": "What genre is the film Manhattan likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19993148744106293,
            "question": "What are some of Woody Allen's most popular works?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Woody Allen stars in the film Manhattan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8828_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Manhattan likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8828_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the film Manhattan probably set?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8828_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous films directed by Woody Allen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8828_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8828_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8828_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8828_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8828_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8828_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8828_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8828_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8828_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8828_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8828_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Woody Allen stars in the film Manhattan. The documents mention that Woody Allen directed and starred in two of his most famous films, Annie Hall and Manhattan. Additionally, there are several instances where Woody Allen is mentioned as being in a scene or picture from the movie Manhattan."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Woody Allen and his film \"Manhattan,\" including that he co-stars in it. Therefore, the statement \"Woody Allen stars in the film Manhattan\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}